http://www.karlproductions.com/privacy-policy

Client Testimonials
What's New?
Contact Us
Privacy Policy
Home/
What We Do/Web VideoTraining VideoDocumentaryTV Spots/PSA's
Case Studies/CASE STUDIES: Web VideosCASE STUDIES: Training VideosCASE STUDIES: DocumentariesCASE STUDIES: PSA/TV Spots
Who We Are/About Karl Productions ChicagoAward Winning Chicago ProducersClient Testimonials
What We Do/Web VideoTraining VideoDocumentaryTV Spots/PSA's
Case Studies/CASE STUDIES: Web VideosCASE STUDIES: Training VideosCASE STUDIES: DocumentariesCASE STUDIES: PSA/TV Spots
Who We Are/About Karl Productions ChicagoAward Winning Chicago ProducersClient Testimonials
What's New?/
Contact Us/
Privacy Policy/
Privacy PolicyWhen accessing or viewing the Karl Productions Website, the user agrees to the terms of our privacy policy which is outlined below. If anyone is not in agreement to the terms listed, they are discouraged from accessing our site.Privacy PolicyThe privacy of our clients is very important to us. Therefore, we have created this page so that you understand how we collect and utilize your information. Here at Karl Productions, we collect information that our clients give us via our contact form. We also collect data that tracks incoming traffic into the site but only in numeric terms. Your identity is anonymous. Both our metric information and the information you provide are saved on our secured server.Karl Productions does not sell any of the information that is provided, neither public nor private, whatsoever, without the consent of the provider. Any payment information we receive is stored in our secured server. We do not use “Cookies” nor disclose any information to any outside parties.Changes to our Private PolicyIn the event we decide to change our Privacy Policy, we will announce it on this page and provide email notification to our clients of any changes.Contacting usIf you have any questions about our privacy policy please do not hesitate to contact us:www.karlproductions.comKarl Productions1743 N. Harlem AveChicago, Illinois 60707(312) 588-1957
Home/
What We Do/Web VideoTraining VideoDocumentaryTV Spots/PSA's
Case Studies/CASE STUDIES: Web VideosCASE STUDIES: Training VideosCASE STUDIES: DocumentariesCASE STUDIES: PSA/TV Spots
Who We Are/About Karl Productions ChicagoAward Winning Chicago ProducersClient Testimonials
What's New?/
Contact Us/
Privacy Policy/
Chicago Video Production Pros
Karl Productions: Award-winning Chicago video production for 25 years. Web Videos, TV Spots/PSAs, Documentaries, Non-Profit. 312-588-1957.
Twitter Feed
David Beedy
TV Spot for Illinois Secretary of State: http://t.co/lJZWHctXTB via @YouTube
Jun 1, 2015, 7:58 AM
David Beedy
Karl Productions creates New TV Spot for Illinois Secretary of State http://t.co/361hURsru6
Jun 1, 2015, 7:10 AM
David Beedy
Organ Donor - Long form Video: http://t.co/E1nvGil1Uz via @YouTube
Apr 1, 2015, 8:06 PM
David Beedy
Organ Donor PSA - TV30: http://t.co/sazvnTRT18 via @YouTube
Apr 1, 2015, 8:02 PM
Copyright, 2015, Karl Productions, Inc.Privacy PolicySearch Engine Optimization Copyright © 2015
Website Optimized by: Elliottsweb.com
.
